魔兽中...
非常好 再前进几步...
all right,just a few more feet. And...
准备好 先生们 Elzebob大门到了
here we are,gentlemen,the gates of elzebob.
上帝啊
Good lord.
东西容器 必属精品
添加微信公众号：ABContainer 获取更多剧集
别慌 坚持97小时的战斗就为了这一刻
Don't panic. This is what the last 97 hours have been about.
待着别动 一群装备武器的地精
Stay frosty. There's a horde of armed goblins
正在门的另一边 守卫着艾辛诺斯之刃
on the other side of that gate guarding the sword of asaroth.
战士们 拔出你们的武器 法师们 举起你们的魔杖
Warriors,unsheathe your weapons. Magic wielders,raise your wands.
准备好了
Lock and load.
拉杰 推开大门
Raj,blow the gates.
推开大门
Blowing the gates.
Control Shift...
Control shift...
B!
天啊 那么多地精!
oh,my god,so many goblins!
别傻站在那里 向前开路! 向前开路!
Don't just stand there,slash and move,slash and move!
保持阵形!
Stay in formation!
谢尔顿 有个敌人在你背后
Leonard,you got one on your tail.
没事 我脑后长眼着呢 我会干掉他的
That's all right,my tail's prehensile- - I'll swat him off.
我打中他了 谢尔顿
I got him,leonard.
今晚我要用那地精的血来祭酒
Tonight I spice my mead with goblin blood.
拉杰 不要 这是个陷阱! 他们在夹击我们!
Raj,no,it's a trap! They're flanking us!
我被打中了!
He's got me!
谢尔顿 他打中拉杰了 快用你的催眠咒!
Sheldon,he's got raj. Use your sleep spell!
Sheldon Sheldon?
Sheldon... sheldon?
我拿到了艾辛诺斯之刃!
I've got the sword of asaroth!
别管剑了 谢尔顿 快救拉杰!
Forget the sword,sheldon,help raj!
我不再是谢尔顿了
There is no more sheldon.
我是剑圣!
I am the sword master!
谢尔顿 当心!
Leonard,look out!
该死 我们快不行了!
Damn it,man,we're dying here!
再见了 土人们!
Good - bye,peasants!
那混蛋走了!
the bastard teleported!
他在Ebay上出售那把艾辛诺斯之刃
He's selling the sword of asaroth on ebay.
你为了钱背叛我们? 你怎么这样?
You betrayed us for money? Who are you?
我是暗夜精灵盗贼 你们没有读过角色介绍吗?
I'm a rogue night elf. Don't you people read character descriptions?
等等! 有人点击了"立即购买"
Wait,wait,wait! Somebody just clicked "buy it now.
我是剑圣!
" I am the sword master!
* 宇宙是个大火炉 *
Our whole universe was in a hot,dense state
* 140亿年前大爆炸 哦稍等 *
then nearly 14 billion years go expansion started... wait!
* 地球开始冷却 生物开始繁衍 *
The earth began to cool the autotrophs began to drool,
* 尼安得特尔人发明工具*
neanderthals developed tools
* 我们建造墙瓦 *
we built the wall
* 我们创造金字塔 数学 科学 历史 *
we built the pyramids
* 揭露奥秘 *
math, science,history, unraveling the mystery
* 就从宇宙大爆炸开始! *
that all started with a big bang bang!
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第03集
The.Fuzzy.Boots.Corollary
哦 我身上都是汗  谁想再进入游个泳?
Ooh,I'm all sweaty. Anybody want to log on to second life and go swimming?
我刚建了个虚拟游泳池
I just built a virtual pool.
不 我现在不想看见你或是你的兽身
No. I can't look at you or your avatar right now.
好像是隔壁的声音
sounds like your neighbor's home.
失陪
Excuse me.
别忘了带上你"无意"拿到的信件
Don't forget the mail you took accidentally on purpose
这样你就有借口跟她说话了
so you'd have an excuse to talk to her.
噢 对 对
Oh,right,right,right,right.
偷窃信箱邮件 很老套的方法 我喜欢
Stealing snail mail, very old school. I like it.
佩妮 邮差又...  哦 抱歉
Penny,the mailman,did it again... he... oh,sorry.
嗨 谢尔顿 这是道格
Um,oh,hi,leonard. This is doug.
道格 这是我邻居谢尔顿
Doug,this is my neighbor leonard.
有事吗 老兄?
What's up,bro?
没什么...
Not much...
老兄
bro.
一切还好吧?
Is everything okay?
是啊 我只是...  我又错拿了你的信 给你
Yeah,no,I just... I got your mail again. Here.
谢谢 我得和邮差说说了
Thank you. I've got to talk to that mailman.
不 这主意不怎么好
Oh,no,that's probably not such a good idea.
人民公仆总是非常容易...动粗
You know,civil servants have a documented propensity to,you know,snap,so...
好吧 还是谢谢你
okay. Well,thank you again.
没问题 再见
No problem. Bye.
哦 再见...老兄
Oh,and bye... bro.
呆呆地在想什么呢? (此谚语中正好有佩妮一词)
Penny for your thoughts.
怎么回事?
What's the matter?
我很好 佩妮也很好
I'm fine. Penny's fine.
和她接吻的家伙也很好
The guy she's kissing is really fine.
接吻 哪一种? 脸颊? 嘴唇? 情人? 朋友?
Kissing? What kind of kissing? Cheeks, lips, chase, French?
你什么毛病啊?
What is wrong with you?
我是个浪漫主义者
I'm a romantic.
别告诉我你不可救药的迷恋
Please don't tell me that your hopeless infatuation
发展成了无意义的嫉妒
is devolving into pointless jealousy.
我不是嫉妒 只是有点担心她
I'm not jealous. I'm just a little concerned for her.
我不怎么喜欢那家伙的长相
I didn't like the look of the guy that she was with.
因为他长得比你帅气?
Because he looks better than you?
是啊
Yeah.
可以说是梦幻般的外形
He was kind of dreamy.
只是你现在还能从燃烧的废墟里
Well,at least now you can retrieve the black box from the twisted,
找回装满对她美妙幻想的黑匣子
olsmdering wreckage that was once your fantasy of dating her
好好分析下数据 你就不会再坠入"呆子谷"
and analyze the data so that you don't crash into geek mountain again.
我反对 爱情不是短跑 而是马拉松
I disagree. Love is not a sprint. It's a marathon.
永不放弃地追逐 直到她最终投入你的怀抱
a relentless pursuit that only ends when she falls into your arms...
或是用防狼喷雾剂喷你
or hits you with the pepper spray.
不 我和佩妮结束了
No,I'm done with penny.
我要更现实些 去追求合我拍的人
I'm going to be more realistic and go after someone my own speed.
比如谁?
Like who?
不知道... 奥利维亚·盖格
I don't know... olivia geiger.
自助餐厅里那个有点跛 还有弱视的营养学家?
The dietician at the cafeteria with the limp and the lazy eye?
是的
Yeah.
哦 我看你没戏
Oh,I don't think you have a shot there.
我注意到莱斯利·温克 最近在刮她的腿毛
I have noticed that leslie winkle recently started shaving her legs.
既然冬天都已经到了
Now given that winter is coming,
只能说明她是在暗示 她可以作为做爱对象
one can only assume she's signaling sexual availability.
我不清楚 你们在同一个实验室
I don't know. You guys work in the same lab.
所以呢?
So?
这有隐患 相信我 我清楚
There are pitfalls. Trust me,I know.
说到性骚扰的相关法律 我可是自学而成的专家
When it comes to sexual harassment law,I'm a bit of a self taught expert.
霍华德 如果我要约莱斯利·温克出去 也只是吃顿饭
Look,howard,if I were to ask leslie winkle out,it would just be for dinner.
我不会去实验室  要她为我跳脱衣舞
I'm not going to walk into the lab,ask her to strip naked and dance for me.
哦 那你就没事了
Oh,then you're probably okay.
嗨 莱斯利
Hello,leslie.
嗨 谢尔顿
Hi,leonard.
莱斯利 我建议做个实验...
Leslie,I would like to propose an experiment...
- 戴上眼镜 谢尔顿 - 好吧
- goggles,leonard. - Right.
莱斯利 我建议做个实验
Leslie,I would like p toropose an experiment.
等一下
Hang on.
我想试试一个500千瓦氧碘激光器
I'm trying to see how long it takes a 500 - kilowatt oxygen iodine laser
得花多久把我的杯装泡面加热
to heat up my cup a' noodles.
我试过 大概2秒 蔬菜汤花2.6秒
I've done it. About two seconds. 2. 6 for minestrone.
总之 我在考虑来个生物学的社交探索
anyway,I was thinking more of a bio- social exploration
结合神经化学方面的专家知识
with a neuro- chemical overlay.
等等 你约我出去?
Wait,are you asking me out?
我认为是改变我们
I was going to characterize it as the modification
同事/友谊关系的范例
of our colleague- slash- friendship paradigm
外加个约会作为补充成分
with the addition of a date like component,
但我们不需要一直说术语
but we don't need to quibble over terminology.
你计划做怎样的实验?
What sort of experiment would you propose?
这个领域有种普遍接受的模式
There's a generally accepted pattern in this area.
我去接你 带你去餐厅
I would pick you up,take you to a restaurant.
接着我们可以看场电影
Then we would see a movie,
也许一部休·格兰特或桑德拉·布洛克
probably a romantic comedy featuring the talents
天才演绎的浪漫轻喜剧
of hugh grant or sandra bullock.
有意思
Interesting.
你是否同意
And would you agree that the primary way
我们评价约会成败的依据
we would evaluate either the success or failure of the date would be based
是基于离别之吻时的化学反应?
on the biochemical reaction during the good night kiss?
心跳率 生化信息素等等 的确
Heart rate,pheromones,etc. Yes.
我们干嘛不假定约会很顺利 直接进行关键的有变数的部分?
Why don't we just stipulate that the date goes well and move to the key variable?
你意思是现在就吻你?
You mean kiss you now?
是的
Yes.
你怎么定义吻的参数吗?
Can you define the parameters of the kiss?
嘴唇的亲密度还有浪漫度 要薄荷吗?
Close - mouthed but romantic. Mint?
谢谢
Thank you.
我数三下?
shall I count down from three?
不 我觉得应该自然点
No,I think it needs to be spontaneous.
感觉怎么样?
What do you think?
你提出的实验方案  该由你先说说实验的发现
You proposed the experiment. I think you should present your findings first.
很公平
Fair enough.
从正面讲 这个吻很不错
On the plus side,it was a good kiss.
合理的技术 没有多余的唾沫
Reasonable technique,no extraneous spittle.
另一方面讲 没什么感觉
On the other hand,no arousal.
- 没感觉? - 没有
- None? - None.
呃 很感谢你抽出时间
Well,thank you for your time.
谢谢你
Thank U.
一点感觉都没?
None at all?
谢尔顿 如果你是机器人 我知道但你自己不知道...
Sheldon,if you were a robot,and I knew and you didn'T... ...
你希望我告诉你吗?
would you want me to tell you?
看情况
That depends.
当我得知我是机器人...
When I learn that I'm a robot...
我有能力承受吗?
will I be able to handle it?
也许吧 虽然历来的科幻小说 都不能苟同这点
Maybe- - although the history of science fiction is not on your side.
好吧 我来问你
Okay,uh,let me ask you this- -
当我得知我是机器人
when I learn that I'm a robot,
我要受限于阿西莫夫的"机器人三定律"吗?
would I be bound by asimov's three laws of robotics?
以下问题均出自"机器人三定律"
你可能现在就受限哦
You might be bound by them right now.
就是啊
That's true.
你伤害过人类吗?
Have you ever harmed a human being
或任人受伤而袖手旁观?
or through inaction allowed a human being to come to harm?
当然没有
Of course not.
除非在他人危险的情况下 你会伤害自己
Have you ever harmed yourself or allowed yourself to be harmed except in cases
或容忍自己被伤害吗?
where a human being would have been endangered?
呃 没有
Well,no.
我闻到机器人的味道了
I smell robot.
嘿 过得怎么样?
Hey,what's going on?
互联网瘫痪半个小时了
Internet's been down for half an hour.
还有 谢尔顿可能是机器人
Also,sheldon may be a robot.
和莱斯利怎么样啦?
So how'd it go with leslie?
哦 我们试着接吻 但地球没转
Oh,we tried kissing,but the earth didn't move.
我是说 比地球原来转的383英里要更多
I mean,any more than the 383 miles that it was going to move anyway.
哦 我以前看过他这表情
Oh,I've seen that look before.
未来两周 他将不停地拖地
This is just going to be two weeks of moping
哼唱乏味的情感歌曲
and tedious emo songs
要我下去宠物商店看猫
and calling me to come down to pet stores to look at cats.
我不知道撑不撑得住
I don't know if I can take it.
你可以关掉自己的电源
You could power down.
一如既往 沃罗威茨会有解决办法的
Well,as usual,wolowitz has the solution.
我碰巧知道个好地方 有很多符合条件的女士
I happen to know a place where there are plenty of eligible women
谢尔顿可以任意选
and leonard could have his pick.
记住拉丁舞的技巧
remember the latin hips.
肩膀挺直 然后摇摆
Shoulders stay still,and... we sway.
一 二 三...
One,two,three... ...
五 六 七
five,six,seven.
媞诗曼女士一直盯着你呢
I think mrs. Tishman's got her eye on you.
我有过经验 你会喜欢的
I've been there. You're in for a treat.
"她说 你不了解我"
She said,"you don't know me"
"你甚至不在乎"
"you don't even care"
"哦 耶"
oh,yeah...
哦 上帝
oh,good lord.
"她说 你不了解我"
She said,"you don't know me"
"你不戴我送你的项链"
"you don't wear my chains"
"哦 耶" 天啊 这歌真棒
oh,yeah. God,that's a good song.
当然 如果这是你为双重自杀混合录制的Cd
If you're compiling a mix cd for a double suicide.
我希望那"猫抓柱"是你自己用的
Oh,I hope that scratching post is for you.
我知道你在想什么 你的哮喘病我有考虑在内
I know what you're thinking. I've taken your asthma into account.
圣地亚哥有个研究猫科的遗传学家
There's a feline geneticist in san diego
培育了一种超可爱的低变应原小猫
who's developed the cutest little hypoallergenic calicos.
谢尔顿 听我说...
Leonard,listen to me...
我在想给它起什么名字
I've been thinking about names.
在爱因斯坦 牛顿和毛靴中士之间犹豫
I'm kind of torn between einstein,newton and sergeant fuzzy boots.
谢尔顿 你真认为养一只转基因猫
Leonard,do you really think you can satisfy your need
可以满足你的感情需要吗?
for a relationshh witip a genetically altered cat?
也许
Maybe.
一只让人爱不释手的可爱小猫
If it's a cute,little,cuddly cat.
得了吧 谢尔顿...
Oh,come on. Leonard...
这都是因为佩妮吧
this is obviously about penny.
没所谓
It doesn't matter.
她对我不感兴趣 拒绝了我
The woman's not interested in me. The woman rejected me.
好吧 听着
Okay,look,
我认为你能跟佩妮做爱的几率
I think that you have as much of a chance of having a sexual relationship with penny
跟哈勃太空望远镜 发现在每个黑洞中央
as the hubble telescope does of discovering at the center of every black hole
都有个小人在用闪光灯 寻找断路器的几率一样大
is a little man with a flashlight searching for a circuit breaker.
尽管如此
Nevertheless,
我还是有责任向你指出 她并没有拒绝你
I do feel obligated to point out to you that she did not reject you.
你从没邀请她去约会
You did not ask her out.
你说的对
You're right.
我没请她约会过 我该去请她约会
I didn't ask her out. I should ask her out.
不不不 重点不是这个
No,no,now that was not my point.
重点是 不要养猫
My point was don't buy a cat.
不 你是对的
No,but you're right.
我该过去请她约会
I should march over there and ask her out.
天 我们要养猫了
Oh,goody,we're getting a cat.
啊...不
Uh... no.
你好 谢尔顿
Oh,hey,leonard.
下午好 佩妮 嗨 你好
Good afternoon,penny. So,hi... hey.
呃...
Uh...
你约了人吃饭吗?
I was wondering if you had plans for dinner.
今晚的饭?
Uh,you mean dinner tonight?
"饭"这个词本身就意思含糊
There is an inherent ambiguity in the word "dinner.
严格说来它所指的是一日的主餐  可以是午餐或晚餐
" Technically it refers to the largest meal of the day whenever it's consumed.
为了说清楚 我指的是晚饭
So to clarify here,by dinner I mean supper.
- 晚饭? - 就是吃饭啦
- Supper? - Or dinner.
如果你有空 6点半行吗? 或者其他你方便的时间
I was thinking 6:30 if you can go. Or a different time.
6点半可以啊
Uh,6:30's great.
真的?
Really?
太好了
Great.
我喜欢跟你们一起玩
Yeah,I like hanging out with you guys.
我们?
Us guys?
对 谢尔顿 霍华德 拉杰 他们都一起吧?
Yeah,you know,sheldon,howard,raj. Who all's coming?
他们...可能都会去吧
They... might all be there.
或者他们中的有些人可能去
Or a subset of them might be there.
从代数角度看 太多未知数了
Algebraically speaking,there are too many unknowns.
比如 谢尔顿中午吃了Quizno三明治
For example,sheldon had quiznos for lunch.
有时他觉得吃那个饱 有时候不觉得
Sometimes he finds that filling,other times he doesn'T.
这不是店家的错 他们的菜单很丰盛
It's no fault of quiznos- - they have a varied menu.
好吧 无所谓啦 听起来挺有意思的
Okay,whatever. It sounds like fun.
很好 我们约时间了吗?
Great. Did we say a time?
6点半
6:30.
- 你确定那时有空? - 对
- And that's still good for you? - It's fine.
- 不是刻在石板上非得那时去哦 - 6点半正好
- 'Cause it's not carved in stone. - No,6:30's great.
我去拿凿子
I'll get my chisel.
为什么?
Why?
去刻在石...6点半见
To... carve the... I'll see you at 6:30.
我看起来如何?
How do I look?
你能说具体一点吗?
Could you be more specific?
能看出来我在冒汗吗?
Can you tell I'm perspiring a little?
不能
No.
你腋下深色的新月状图案 将其隐藏的很好
The dark crescent shaped patterns under your arms conceal it nicely.
你几点约会?
What time is your date?
6点半
6:30.
太好了 那你还有2小时15分
Perfect. That gives you two hours and 15 minutes for
让那片稠密的人造纤维分子云消散
that dense molecular cloud of aramis to dissipate.
汗很多吗?
Is it too much?
如果你是橄榄球队员就不算多
Not if you're a rugby team.
如果以后提到今晚的事 你没来参加的原因是
By the way,if it should ever come up,you didn't join us
你在Quiznos吃鸡肉三明治吃撑了
because you stuffed yourself with a chicken carbonara sub at quiznos.
我为什么要去参加?
Why would I join you?
不为什么
No reason.
你知道吗 也许这样做不好
Oh,you know what,maybe this isn't such a good idea.
不 酒精加上她一时糊涂
Oh,no,well,now there's always the possibility that alcohol and poor judgment
总有可能让今晚成为浪漫之夜
on her part might lead to a nice romantic evening.
你说的对 酒 糊涂 今晚有可能会顺利的
You're right. Alcohol,poor judgment- - it could go well.
当然还有另一种可能性
Of course there is the other possibility,
之后的6个月都会很难捱
that this date kicks off a rather unpleasant six months
俩人在走廊里尴尬的擦身而过
of the two of you passing awkwardly in the hall,
直到其中一人崩溃并搬到别的州去
until one of you breaks down and moves to another zip code.
你说到"可能会顺利"就可以闭嘴了
You could've stopped at "it could go well.
"如果我能 我会的"
" If I could've,I would've.
我是绝种好男人
I mean,I'm a perfectly nice guy.
没理由我们不能 在餐厅吃好顿晚餐
There's no reason we couldn't go to the restaurant,and have a lovely dinner,
饭后散散步 聊些共同话题
maybe take a walk afterwards,talk about things we have in common.
"你喜欢陶艺? 我超爱陶艺的!"
You love pottery? I love pottery!
然后暂停一下 我们都知道接下来要发生什么
There's a pause,we both know what's happening.
我倾身向前 我俩接吻
I lean in,we kiss.
开始时还有点犹豫 然后她开始回吻我
It's a little tentative at first,but then I realize she's kissing me back.
她在咬我的下唇! 她想要我!
She's biting my lower lip! She wants me!
这事能成!我们会做爱!
This thing is going the distance! We're going to have sex!
天 上帝啊!
Oh,god,oh,my god!
现在开始做爱了?
Is the sex starting now?
我恐慌症发作了
I'm having a panic attack.
好吧 冷静点
Oh,okay. Uh,well then... calm down.
如果我能冷静 就不会恐慌了!
If I could calm down,I wobe having a panic att...
不然这怎么叫做恐慌症发作!
that's why they call it a panic attack.
好好 你坐下
All right,all right. Uh,s- s- sit down.
坐下 闭上眼
Yeah,sit down. Now close your eyes.
- 为什么? - 照做吧!
- Why? - Just do it.
好
Okay.
α波是脑电图中最著名的一种波在正常成年人闭眼放松时产生
试着增加你α波的活性
Now try to increase your alpha wave activity.
什么? !
What? !
这是机能反馈疗法
It's a biofeedback technique.
通过控制脑电波来放松
It's relaxation through brain wave manipulation.
我在美国神经科学月刊上 看到一篇关于它的论文
I read a paper about it in journal of american neuroscience.
它的理论来源不完备 但是我认为基本原理正确
It was a little sparsely sourced,but I think the basic science is valid.
我可能把它放在这了
I probably have it here somewher E.
我没法赴这个约会
Who am I kidding? I can't go through with this.
你给她打电话取消吧
You need to call her and cancel.
- 我? - 对
- Me? - Yes.
- 我要跟她说什么? - 我不知道
- What should I tell her? - I don't know.
- 跟她说我病了 - 好
- Tell her I'm sick. - Okay.
别说那种会让她想来照顾我的病
Not the kind of illness that will make her want to come over and take care of me,
也不要严重得让她 以后不愿跟我约会的病
but nothing so critical that she'll feel uncomfortable going out with me in the future
如果我以后还想尝试的话
if I want to try this again.
了解
Got it.
那不能说花柳病啦?
So I'm assuming nothing venereal?
就跟她说你做了例行肠镜检查 还没恢复吧
I'll just tell her that you had a routine conoloscopy and haven't quite bounced back.
给我电话
Give me the phone.
你不是想取消约会吗?
I thought you wanted to cancel.
不行 如果我不出现 她还是会认为你会去的
I can't,because if I don't show up she'll still be expecting you.
为什么她认为我会去?
Why would she be expecting me?
别问了 我要再去洗个澡
Stop asking me all these questions. I need to take another shower.
其他的人直接来这找我们?
So are the rest of the guys meeting us here?
对...不对
Oh,yeah... no.
拉杰跟霍华德要工作 谢尔顿...
It turns out that raj and howard had to work,and sheldon...
做了肠镜 还没恢复过来
had a colonoscopy and he hasn't quite bounced back yet.
我叔叔也做了肠镜
Oh,my uncle just had a colonoscopy.
这就是我们俩的共同之处了
You're kidding. Then that's something we have in common.
怎么说?
How?
我们都认识...
We both have people in our lives who...
想将肠道息肉扼杀于摇篮当中的人
want to nip intestinal polyps in the bud.
物理界有啥新闻不?
so what's new in the world of physics?
没有
Nothing.
真的? 一点都没有?
Really? Nothing?
除了弦理论 自1930年后就没什么发现了
Well,with the exception of string theory, not much has happened since the 1930s.
而弦理论也尚未证明
And you can't prove string theory.
最多就能说
At best you can say,"hey,look,
"嘿 我的理论内部逻辑很连贯"
my idea has an internal logical consistency.
啊
" Ah.
我相信情况会好转的
Well,I'm sure things will pick up.
芝士蛋糕工厂那边有什么新消息?
What's new at the cheesecake factory?
没有什么
Oh,uh,not much.
有个巧克力柠檬派卖得很好
We do have a chocolate key lime that's moving pretty well.
很好
Good. Good.
那你那个...
What about your,uh...
过道上的朋友怎样?
hallway friend?
道格? 我不知道
Doug? Oh,yeah,I don't know.
他人挺好也很风趣 但是...
I mean,you know,he's nice and funny,but...
准备开始点饮品了吗?
can I get you started with some drinks?
不!
No!
- 你刚刚说到? 但是... - 我想喝点东西
- You were saying? But... - I'd like a drink.
先说完关于道格的"但是" 我会把她叫回来
Just say the "but" thing about doug and then I'll get her back.
我不知道 是我的问题
Okay,well,I don't know,it's just me.
我还没从跟科特的分手中完全恢复
I'm still getting over this breakup with kurt
跟道格在一起是为了复健性爱
and this thing with doug would stju be rebound sex.
噢 提起复健性爱啊...
Oh,don't get me started on rebound sex.
我总是这样
It's just... it's my pattern.
分手后找个帅哥
I break up,then I find some cute guy,
然后就是36小时毫无意义的...
and then it's just 36 meaningless hours of...
你知道
you know.
我不确定我知道
I'm not sure that I do.
是连续36个小时
is that one 36-hour experience,
还是一个辉煌夏季中...
or is that 36 hours spread out over,say...
分散的36个小时?
one glorious summer?
不 大概是一个周末吧
No,it's usually over a weekend,
相信我 那之后感觉很不好
and trust me,you do not feel good after it.
呃 皮肤疼痛是吧?
Well,chafing,right?
心情不好
Emotionally.
没错 心里疼痛
Of course,yeah,emotional chafing.
你想看些有趣的玩意吗?
Hey,do you want to see something cool?
我不用手碰 就能把这颗橄榄弄进杯子里
I can make this olive go into this glass without touching it.
- 怎么弄啊? - 物理原理
- How? - Physics.
哇 离心力
Wow,centrifugal force.
实际上 是向心力
Actually,it's centripetal force,
玻璃对橄榄作用产生的内向力
which is an inward force generated by the glass acting on the olive...
抱歉
Excuse me.
如果你坐在那颗橄榄上
If you were riding on the olive,
你就是一个非惯性参照系 并会...
you'd be in a non - inertial reference frame and would...
你没事吧?
are you okay?
没事
Yeah,I'm okay.
你打翻花生酱了吗?
Did you spill ketchup?
- 没 - 那有事了
- No. - I'm not okay.
你确定不用去急诊室?
Are you sure you don't want to go to the emergency room?
我没事 不流血了
No,no,I'm okay. It stopped bleeding.
但你吐了啊  那不是脑震荡的症状吗?
I know,but you did throw up. Isn't that a sign of a concussion?
对 但我也晕车 所以...
Yes. But I get car sick,too,so...
好吧
okay.
还有 抱歉弄脏你的车
Sorry about your car,by the way.
没关系 大部分你都吐车外了
Oh,no,it's fine. You got most of it out the window.
那个骑自行车的可怜人
The poor guy on the bike.
我今晚过得很愉快
Well,I had a nice time.
我也是
Yeah,me,too.
那晚安啦
Well,um,good night.
晚安
Good night.
- 谢尔顿? - 啊?
- Leonard? - Ahye?
今晚这是约会吗?
Was this supposed to be a date?
今晚?
This?
不是
No.
当然不是
No,of course not.
只是你跟我还有一帮
This was just you and me hanging out with a bunch of guys
因工作和肠镜而没有出现的人的聚会
who didn't show up 'cause of work and a colonoscopy.
好 我只是问问
Okay,I was just checking.
如果我跟女孩约会 我确实跟女孩约会
When I take a girl on a date- - and I do- -
那个女孩会知道她是在约会的
she knows she's been dated.
大写D
Capital D.
粗体黑字 下划线
boldface. Undeinrled.
约 会
Da... ted.
我可能脑震荡了 我去躺躺
I think I might have a little concussion. I'm gonna go lie down.
晚安
Good night.
约会如何?
So,how was your date?
赞!
Awesome!
凭 酒和糊涂 得一分
Score one for liquor and poor judgment.